<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dee van der Knaap</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Dee van der Knaap</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating maps using Leaflet for R: Who participates in online experiments?</title>
      <link>/creating-maps-using-leaflet-for-r-who-participates-in-online-experiments/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/creating-maps-using-leaflet-for-r-who-participates-in-online-experiments/</guid>
      <description>One of my goals last semester, aside from learning a ton more statistical methods in R in my Applied Data Analysis and Statistical Inference class, was to get more hands-on experience creating automated visualization tools. The goal was two-fold: to learn to play around (and fight with) tools in R and Python, as well as to hopefully create web-based data tools that could contribute to the open-science community and make data visualization simpler and instantaneous for anyone with an internet connection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a current student at Wellesley College with eclectic interests in statistics, health, innovation &amp;amp; development, and ethics. I am passionate about data science, open science initiatives, reproducibility, epidemiology, and neuroscience.
Read my blog to follow my personal musings and projects.
Website style based off of example website for the blogdown package. The theme was forked from @jrutheiser/hugo-lithium-theme and modified by Yihui Xie.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>